MIRCrew发布
MIRCrew Releases
你好！
Buona visione!!!
装载工作已经完成，准备起飞了一半。
The loading operations are finish, half ready for take-off.
有什么问题吗，中士？
There a problem, Sergeant?
不，先生..。
No, sir...
抱歉，我只是...
Sorry, I was just, uh--
把你的狗屎收拾好。我们五分钟后起飞。
Get your shit together. We lift off in five.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
嘿，你有光环资格，对吧？
Hey, you're HALO qualified, yeah?
光环？
HALO?
不，不对。
No, sir.
我们是在做光晕跳跃吗？
Are we doing a HALO jump?
你会没事的。
You'll be fine.
我会去水果圈。
I'd go Fruit Loops.
我女儿很喜欢它们。
My daughter loves them.
米切尔中尉报道。我重复一遍。
Lieutenant Mitchell reporting. I repeat.
米切尔中尉报道。
Lieutenant Mitchell reporting.
啊，他妈的。
Ah, fuck.
追捕一名被俘虏的中情局线人。
Going after a CIA asset that's been captured.
计划是以最小的伤亡救出他。
The plan is to extract him with minimal casualties.
他在收集俄罗斯军火商亚历山大·彼得罗夫的情报
He was gathering intel on Alexander Petrov, a Russian arms dealer
和前克格勃。
and former KGB.
出什么事啦？
What's up?
那是你的家人吗？
That your family?
不，只是头盔上的一张照片。
Nah, just a pic that came with the helmet.
嗯。妻子和孩子。
Yeah. Wife and kids.
好的。
Nice.
这些是新的5.11战术手套吗？
Are those the new 5.11 tactical gloves?
你知道有凯夫拉尔针织衫的那种吗？
You know the ones with the Kevlar knit?
是啊，是啊。凯夫拉尔针织。
Yeah, yeah. Kevlar knit.
太棒了。
Awesome.
JTAC，
JTAC,
试着放松，好吗？
just try to relax, okay?
回到欧洲杯的另一条路上，让那个球离开。
Right back the other way on the Euro and gets that one to go.
哨子也响了。
And the whistle too...
有那么糟吗？
That bad?
是啊，就那么糟。
Yeah, that bad.
你想谈谈吗？
Do you wanna talk about it?
想拥抱一下吗？
Wanna hug?
我们可以拥抱一下。
We can hug.
你需要我吗？
You need me?
是的，我想问你一些事，但是……
Yeah, I wanted to ask you something, but...
好吧。咖啡?
Okay. Coffee?
好的。
Sure.
好吧。
Okay.
嗯。
Yeah.
凉爽的。
Cool.
所以，呃，
So, uh,
你知道婚礼快到了，对吧？
you know the wedding's coming up, right?
是的，我知道。第二十三。
Yes, I do. Twenty-third.
没错。
That's right.
你不会改日期的，是吗？
You're not gonna change the date, are you?
什么？
What?
我已经把一切都安排好了。我让孩子们就位了。
I've got everything organized. I got the kids in place.
我把前妻都安排好了。
I got the ex-wives in place.
-露西会出院的。-收割者。
- Lucy will be out of the hospital. - Reaper.
我不会更改日期的。我，
I'm not going to change the date. I,
呃，其实我想和你谈点别的事。
um, actually wanted to talk to you about something else.
我想问--
I wanted to ask--
谁动了我的屎？
Who moved my shit?
飞行员..。
Airman...
谁动了我的屎？
who moved my shit?
哈?
Huh?
咖啡豆。
Coffee pods.
我不知道，先生。我用点滴。
I-- I don't know, sir. I use the drip.
那么，你说的话我一个字都不能相信，对吧？
Well, I can't trust a word you say then, can I?
嗯。
Yeah.
我从容不迫。
I take the time.
每天他妈的早上。
Every goddamn morning.
我做这件事
I do it
为了提高效率，
for efficiency,
容易辨认，
easy recognition,
和组织能力。
and organization.
它被欣赏了吗？
Is it appreciated?
不是的。
No.
它是受人尊敬的。
It is respected.
我想不会。
I think not.
但我会这么做
But I do it
为了鼓舞士气
for the morale
中队的。
of the squadron.
你刚才说什么来着？
You were saying?
行动将在15分钟后开始。
Op starts in 15.
是啊，是啊。我以为你有话要说呢。
Yeah, yeah. I thought you wanted to talk about something.
可以等一等。
It can wait.
他妈的。
Shit.
你丢了什么东西？
You lose something?
啊，只是我的麦片。
Ah, just my cereal.
你的什么？
Your what?
弗罗特循环。
Froot Loops.
我有一盒果仁圈饼。我不知道我用它做了什么。
I had a box of Froot Loops. I don't know what I did with it.
上帝啊，空军。
Jesus Christ, Air Force.
刚刚开始这次行动，你就已经在为一盒糖霜薄片而汗流浃背了。
Barely started this op and you're already sweating about a box of Frosted Flakes.
不，不。那是--那是果仁圈。
No, no. It was-- it was Froot Loops.
哈?
Huh?
是果仁圈，不是霜冻薄片。
Froot Loops, not Frosted Flakes.
这孩子是真的吗？
This kid for real?
别像个混蛋一样。
Don't be an asshole.
真可爱啊。
That's cute.
谢谢你，伙计。
Thanks, man.
他妈的水果圈。
Fucking Fruit Loops.
你多大了，空军？
How old are you, Air Force?
二十七岁。
Twenty-seven.
啊.。
Ah...
毕晓普，你女儿现在多大了？二十?
Bishop, how old's your daughter now? Twenty?
你应该给空军安排个约会。
You should set Air Force up on a date.
嗯。我会一枪打死你的，阿贝尔。我对天发誓。
Yeah. I will shoot you in the dick, Abell. I swear to God.
不，亲爱的。
No, honey.
我不行。
I can't.
我不能去。
I can't come.
因为我必须在这里
'Cause I gotta be here
在工作中。嗯。
at work. Yeah.
听着，让你妹妹走就行了。
Look, just get your sister to go.
那你妈妈呢？
What about your mom?
好的。嗯，你为什么不打电话给……？
All right. Well, why don't you call...?
哦，你给朱迪打电话了？呃..。
Oh, you called Judy? Uh...
听着，好的，好的。
look, okay, okay.
如果只是几件事，那也没问题。
If it's only a couple of things, that's fine.
那很好。但现在，我得走了
That's fine. But right now, I gotta go
因为我有任务，对吧？
'cause I got a mission, yeah?
泽格勒流了一小滴眼泪。
Zegler a little teardrop.
你知道我不喜欢大学里的那张照片，对吧？
You know I don't like that shot in college, right?
它的制作大约是Tirt--是的，
It's made about thirt-- yeah,
它制作的几率约为37%。
it's made about 37 percent of the time.
操。
Fuck.
泽格勒刚刚满足于在地板的第一侧有一个强硬的漂浮者。
Zegler just settled for a tough floater on the first side of the floor.
伙计们。
Guys.
我想请你帮个忙。
I got a favor to ask you.
我妻子怀孕了。
My wife is pregnant.
我在手术室的时候，如果她要生了，她会打那个电话的。
While I'm on OP, if she goes into labor, she's gonna call that phone.
好的?
All right?
你需要接电话，
You need to answer it,
你得过来接我。
and you need to come and get me.
收到了吗？
Copy?
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
为什么我们不把音量调低一点呢？
And why don't we just keep this volume down to a low level?
因为这是一个专业的工作环境。
Because this is a professional work environment.
好了，好了。只是因为你的团队
Now, now. Just because your team
带来了三月疯狂历史上最大的窒息，
delivered the biggest choke in March Madness history,
并不意味着我们其他人就不能尽情享受。
doesn't mean the rest of us can't still enjoy ourselves.
是关于露西的。维吉尔，这很重要。
It's about Lucy. Virgil, it's important.
我知道呀。
I know.
注意到，呃，
Notice the, uh,
假性毛囊炎
pseudofolliculitis
Barbae还没有
barbae hasn't
弄清楚了。
cleared up.
还没有，先生。不是的。
Not yet, sir. No.
好的，你只要告诉我你什么时候准备好刮胡子。
Well, you just let me know when you're ready to shave.
我会的，先生。
I will, sir.
好的。
All right.
加油，沃斯！-加油，沃斯！
- Go, Vols! - Go, Vols!
战鹰，这里是黑鸟接近降落区。
Warhawk, this is Blackbird approaching drop zone.
正飞向15000英尺的高空。
Headed to 15,000 feet.
六分钟就到DZ了。
Six minutes to the DZ.
风速为5海里/小时，东南风。
Winds are five knots and to the southeast.
天空晴朗。
Skies are clear.
祝你狩猎愉快。
Happy hunting.
好了，伙计们。六分钟。
All right, boys. Six minutes.
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
水果圈，现在是时候检查你的武器了。
Fruit Loop, now's the time to be checking your weapon.
我很好。
I'm good.
不是你的游戏机。你的真实武器。
Not your Gameboy. Your actual weapon.
嘿，听着，无人机是我管的。所以..。
Hey, look, I'm in charge of the drone. So...
如果我们陷入困境，而我在开枪，
if we wind up in a situation and I'm shooting,
我们他妈的有大麻烦了。
we got big fucking problems.
你说的没错。
You're not wrong.
你说的没错。JTAC只对一件事有好处，那就是...“带来了雨。”
You're not wrong. JTAC's only good for one thing and that is... "Bringing the rain."
这是你在战区的第一次任务吗，JTAC？
Is this your first mission in theater, JTAC?
第二。
Second.
但首先是运营商。
But first with operators.
什么？
What?
见鬼，我会说的。嗯.。
Hell, I'll say it. Um...
我们就要陷入一场狗屎风暴了。
we're about to head into a shit storm.
你看起来还是需要有人帮你擦屁股。
You still look like you kind of need someone to wipe your ass.
所以你就..。帮我个忙。
So just... do me a favor.
跟上，别他妈的搞砸了。
Keep up and don't fuck up.
这次行动我们最不需要的就是救你的命。
Last thing we need in this op is to have to save your ass.
不，他很棒。
Nah, he's good.
嘿,
Hey,
记住你所受的训练。
remember your training.
跟飞机谈谈。
Talk to the planes.
当他们开始投掷炸弹时，确保落在坏人身上。
When they start dropping bombs, make sure it's on the bad guys.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
你不会需要这些的。
You're not going to need these.
这是一次无菌手术。
This is a sterilized op.
请注意，我们正在接近...
Be advised we are approaching--
好了，伙计们。让我们戴上口罩吧。我们开始工作吧。
All right, boys. Let's put our masks on. Let's get to work.
嘿，JTAC
Hey, JTAC,
这可能听起来很愚蠢，但别忘了呼吸，好吗？
this might sound stupid but don't forget to breathe, yeah?
保持通讯畅通。
Stay on your comms.
当这个数字达到3000的时候，
When that hits 3,000,
展开你的降落伞。
deploy your chute.
它和空中的一样，
It's just the same as airborne,
只有他妈的更高。
only way fucking higher.
好了，可以走了。
Good to go.
我会在海滩上见到你们这些混蛋。
I'll see you fuckers on the beach.
啊哈。
Yee-haw.
嘿,
Hey,
在公园里散步。
walk in the park.
操。
Fuck.
你还好吗？
You good?
我们走吧。赶快。起床。
Let's go. Come on. Get up.
那个山脊。
That ridge.
到8点时点击四下。
Four clicks by 0800.
我们走吧。我们走吧。
Let's go. Let's move.
好的。
All right.
先生,
Sir,
谢谢你，米勒。
Thank you, Miller.
好的，队伍已经着陆了。
Okay, team has landed.
接线员已经在路上了。
Operators are en route.
无人驾驶飞机距离会合点有10米远
The drone is ten mics out from rendezvous point
而战鹰正在切换通讯系统。
and Warhawk is switching comms.
这辆马车就要变成南瓜了。
This carriage is about to turn into a pumpkin.
这不是我的椅子。
This is not my chair.
是的，是这样的。
Yes, it is.
不，不是的。
No, it is not.
哦，天哪，死神，我没有坐你的椅子。
Oh, my god, Reaper, I did not take your chair.
我知道你没占我的椅子。
I know you didn't take my chair.
那就是影子飞行中的这些共产主义混蛋。
It will be these commie assholes from Shadow Flight.
你说完了吗？
You finished?
不，我不是。
No, I'm not.
吃一袋鸡巴。
Eat a bag of dicks.
现在我说完了。
Now I'm finished.
好吧。
Okay.
好了，我们带这位女士去跳舞吧。
All right, let's take this lady to the dance.
花花公子06，我是收割者1-0.
Playboy 06, this is Reaper 1-0 checking in...
你有一架MQ-9在空中。
You have 1 MQ-9 in the air.
1由BLU 118在船上。还有八个小时的游戏时间。
1 by BLU 118 on board. Eight hours of playtime ahead.
收割者1-0，这是花花公子0-6。各就各位，完毕。
Reaper 1-0, this is Playboy 0-6. Stand by for grid, over.
罗杰。待命中。
Roger. Standing by.
网格，如下所示，
Grid as follows,
…11月，维克多，7岁，内纳，5-7-1-8。
…November, Victor, 7, Niner, 5-7-1-8.
这是一个友好的网格。
That's a friendly grid.
罗杰，花花公子。我在友好网格上看到了。
Roger, Playboy. I have visual on friendly grid.
我是你天空中的眼睛，是厄运的使者。
I am your eyes in the sky and the bringer of doom.
完毕。
Over.
“死神”号已升空。我们的位置已确定。
Reaper is airborne. Our location is confirmed.
条例是什么？
What's the ordinance?
两架地狱火和一架蓝色-118，长官。
Two hellfire's and a BLUE-118, sir.
别管那狗屎先生了。我工作是为了谋生。
Lose the sir shit. I work for a living.
是白糖还是白糖。
It's Sugar or Sug.
好的。
All right.
让他觉得自己老了。
Makes him feel old.
他很老了。
He is old.
谢谢，空军。
Thanks, Air Force.
嘿，JTAC。
Hey, JTAC.
他们是在什么岩石下发现你的？
What rock did they find you under?
在关岛进行训练演习。
In Guam on a training exercise.
错过了班机。
Missed the flight out.
那是
That was
九个小时前。
nine hours ago.
你怎么错过了航班？
How'd you miss the flight?
我的胃有点不舒服。
I had some stomach issues.
等。
Wait.
你来这里是因为你拉屎了？
You're here 'cause you had the shits?
好吧，我希望你把这些都清理干净了。
Well, I hope you got that all cleared out.
你在一次行动中拉屎，
You shit your pants on an op,
那污点将伴随你一生。
that stain will follow you for life.
你听取简报了吗？
Did you get briefed?
是啊，但我有点困惑。
Yeah, but I'm a little confused.
关于?
What about?
好吧，我不是第一层。
Well, I'm not tier one.
但他却走在我们中间。
Yet he walks amongst us.
我以为运营商不会在没有一级员工的情况下外出。
I thought operators don't go out without tier one personnel.
我们没有。
We don't.
那我为什么会在这里？
So why am I here?
JSOC的一项资产在两周前失踪。
A JSOC asset disappeared two weeks ago.
据信是被绑架的。
Believed to be kidnapped.
我们得到了一个可能的地点的情报。
We've got intel on a possible locale.
所以这是一次救援行动？
So this is a rescue op?
有可能。
Potentially.
阿。
Ah.
你永远跟不上这些中情局的间谍。
You can never keep up with these CIA spooks.
不管怎样..。我们到了。
Either way... here we are.
所以回答你的问题..。
So to answer your question...
不，你不应该在这里。
no, you shouldn't be here.
而且，是的，
And, yes,
达美航空通常不会在没有一级员工的情况下离开。
Delta doesn't usually go out without their tier one personnel.
而且，是的，
And, yes,
如果我们的人在这里，
if our guy is here,
那我们就进去他妈的抓他。
then we'll go in and fucking get him.
翻译..。
Translation...
升级你的游戏。
step up your game.
我需要有人掩护我。
I need someone to cover.
嗯。
Yeah.
我得去跟露西报到。
I gotta check in with Lucy.
她怎么样了？
How's she doing?
她太棒了。
She's fantastic.
不过，宝宝的大脑还在继续。
Got the baby brain going on though.
每件事我都要重复五次。
I gotta repeat everything five times.
太棒了。
It's amazing.
绝对是巨大的。
Absolutely huge.
这场婚礼也是这样。
Got the same thing about this wedding.
这是可以理解的。
Uh, it's understandable.
有很多细节。
There's a lot of detail.
你想一想吧。
You think about it.
婚礼可能是人类拥有的最伟大的社交仪式。
A wedding is probably the greatest social ritual humanity has.
你知道,
You know,
你生命中最重要的一天。
most important day of your life.
还不如把它做对。
Might as well get it right.
你只会做一次。
You're only going to do it once.
死神，你已经结过四次婚了。
Reaper, you've been married four times.
是啊，不过这只是我的想法。
Yeah, that's just me though.
我是个浪漫主义者。
I'm a romantic.
你之前想问我什么？
What did you want to ask me before?
哦，我--
Oh, I--
先别着急。
Hold that thought.
谢谢你，米勒。
Thank you, Miller.
收割者。
Reaper.
嘿，怎么了？
Hey, what's up?
啊，这该死的烂摊子真让我头疼。
Ah, this fucking frag is a pain in my ass.
我还以为你已经补好了呢。
Thought you got that patched up.
我做到了。
I did.
那你为什么还在抱怨这件事？
So why are you still bitching about it?
我腿上还有个他妈的洞，混蛋。
There's still a fucking hole in my leg, asshole.
发生了什么？
What happened?
简易爆炸装置。
I.E.D.
有个孩子点击半下就触发了它。
Some kid triggered it from half a click out.
我们一点机会都没有。
We never stood a chance.
问题就在这里，Fruit Loop。
Therein lies the problem, Fruit Loop.
所有这些技术，都需要
All this tech, it takes
战争中的人的因素。
the human element out of warfare.
如果所有这些狗屎都失败了怎么办？
And what happens when all that shit fails?
嗯--
Well--
好吧，那是什么？
Well, what?
我不知道。我是说,
I don't know. I mean,
我认为这项技术可以拯救生命。
I think this tech saves lives.
在某种程度上，它让它失去了野蛮的本质。
In a way, it's takes the barbaric nature out of it.
野蛮的本性？
Barbaric nature?
猪身上的口红。
Lipstick on a pig.
你真的认为你向50个人投掷炸弹比我们朝他们脑袋开枪好吗？
You really think you dropping a bomb on 50 people is any better than us shooting them in the head?
不是的。
No.
不是的。战争是野蛮的。
No. War is barbaric.
这他妈的永远不会改变。
It ain't never gonna fucking change.
它已经做到了。
It already has.
听好了，水果圈。
Listen up, Fruit Loop.
让我给你讲个故事。
Let me tell you a story.
你可以用你想要的机器人、收割机和手机战斗。
You can fight with all your robots and your reapers and cell phones you want.
一天结束的时候，
The end of the day,
当技术失败时
when the technology fails
还有你所有的.
and all your--
你的电池、子弹和炸弹都用完了，你知道，
your batteries and your bullets and your bombs run out, you know,
他妈的太阳爆炸了，
and the fucking sun explodes,
战争归根结底是一件非常简单的事情。
war comes down to one very simple thing.
这就是杀人狂。
And that's man killing man.
只需要一狗屎的一天就能改变你的整个观点。
Just takes one shit day to change your whole perspective.
这是事实。
That's a fact.
嗯。
Yeah.
欢迎来到坏世界。
Welcome to the land of bad.
他妈的故事棒极了，伙计。
Fucking great story, man.
真他妈的好，富有，令人信服。
Really fucking good, rich and compelling.
你查到什么了？
What do you got?
我有动静了。
I got movement.
一百米。
Hundred meters.
就在那些岩石的另一边。
Just the other side of those rocks.
我需要监视那座山脊。东北方向一百米处。
I need eyes over that ridge. Hundred meters northeast.
收割者1-0，这是花花公子0-6。
Reaper 1-0, this is Playboy 0-6.
在我们位置东北方向一百米处有可疑移动。你能帮我查一下吗？
Got suspicious movement a hundred meters northeast of our position. Can you check it out?
收到，花花公子。待命。
Roger that, Playboy. Standby.
东南方向一百米处。
Hundred meters southeast.
握手很好。
Got good handshake.
收割者1-0，你能放大吗？
Reaper 1-0, can you zoom in?
收到。
Copy that.
是啊，哦，太性感了。
Yeah, oh, that's sexy.
左摇摄，50米。
Pan left, 50 meters.
他妈的怎么回事?
What the fuck?
收割者，我中空了，完毕。
Reaper, I'm hollow, over.
罗杰。待命。
Roger. Standby.
系统故障。
Systems malfunction.
该死的狗屎。
Goddamn piece of shit.
花花公子，这只鸟出了系统故障。
Playboy, we have a systems malfunction on the bird.
收到。吊舱在运行吗？
Copy that. Is the pod inop?
那是一家顶级公司，花花公子。我们得把这狗屎送回基地。
That is an a-firm, Playboy. We got to get this piece of shit back to base.
还有其他的鸟吗？
Is another bird available?
这是负面的。
That is a negative.
我们会把这个修好，然后马上送回给你。
We'll fix this one up and get it back to you stat.
收割者被击落。没有其他无人机可用。
Reapers down. No other UAV's available.
《破碎的死神》，是吧？
Broken Reaper, huh?
这难道不是他妈的讽刺吗？
Ain't that some fuckin' irony?
看来我们得用老式的方法越过这座山脊了。艾贝尔，你说对了。
Looks like we're gonna have to clear this ridge the old-fashioned way. Abell, you're on point.
收到。
Copy.
毕晓普
Bishop,
你被留下了。
you're left.
收到。
Copy.
我们剩下的空中支援是什么？
What's the rest of our air support?
大黄蜂待命。三十米外。
Hornet's on standby. Thirty mikes out.
你想让我做什么？
What do you want me to do?
没什么。
Nothing.
我这一头什么都没有。
I got nothing on my end.
这里也一样。
Same here.
看起来没问题。
Looks clear.
等。
Wait.
等等，我有动静了。
Wait, I've got movement.
十米。
Ten meters.
哦，看在他妈的份上。
Oh, for fuck's sake.
这就是他妈的一声呼噜。
It's a fucking oink oink.
见鬼的叫声是什么？
What the hell's an oink oink?
一头该死的猪，笨蛋。
A fucking pig, dumbass.
我很确定你钱包里有她的照片。
Pretty sure you got a picture of her in your wallet.
混蛋。
Fucker.
这是严重的坏人窝点狗屎。
This is serious bad guy lair shit.
桥上有两只探戈。
Got two tangos on the bridge.
最右边的三分之一。
A third on the far right.
帐篷的另一边。
Other side of the tent.
看到下面的星巴克了吗？
See a Starbucks down there?
我在S弯道的下部看到了4号
I see number four on the lower part of the S-bend road
让我们往下推。
Let's push down.
好吧。安全了。
Okay. Clear.
安全了。
Clear.
好吧。我们称它为OP1。空军，
Okay. We're gonna call this OP1. Air Force,
把上面的东西放好。
set up up top.
艾贝尔，你留在原地。准备好你的后见之明。
Abell, you stay put. Set up your hindsight.
毕晓普，你跟我来。
Bishop, you're with me.
我们要绕到东南方向。
We're gonna wrap around southeast.
太好了。
Hooah.
你还好吗？
You good?
是的，我想是的。
Yeah, I think so.
好吧。勇往直前，征服一切。
Okay. Go forth and conquer.
好了，先生们。
All right, gents.
坐着别动。
Sit tight.
喊出你所看到的。在我们行动之前要清点一下那个化合物的人数。
Call out what you see. want a head count on that compound before we move on it.
建议？
Sug?
我们什么时候能在夏威夷得到一场不错的演出？
When can we get a nice gig in Hawaii?
我受够了沼泽裤腿。
Sick of swamp crotch.
我想他们不会再让你回夏威夷了。
I don't think they'd allow you back in Hawaii since last time.
那是
That was
就一次。
one time.
一堆狗屎。上床。
Piece of shit. Fucking.
有动静了。
Got movement.
好的，这看起来就像是我们要找的人。
All right, this sure looks like our guy.
毕晓普，你能确认一下吗？
Bishop, can you confirm?
是的，这就是彼得罗夫。
Yeah, that's Petrov all right.
好吧,
Okay,
如果他在这里，
if he's here,
线人一定很近。
the asset's gotta be close.
迅雷中队？
Thunderbolt Squadron?
不，它不是。
No, it's not.
很抱歉我不能为你做这件事。
I'm sorry I can't do that for you.
你得给接线员回电话。
You're gonna have to call the operator back.
如果你要141分机，那是迅雷。嗯，嗯。
If you ask for extension 141, that's Thunderbolt. Uh-huh.
好的，没问题。
Yeah, no problem.
伙计们。
Guys...
他妈的怎么回事?
what the fuck?
有什么问题吗，船长？
What's the problem, Captain?
我让你留心这部电话。
I asked you to keep an ear on this phone.
某个自作聪明的家伙把铃声关掉了。
Some smartass turned the goddamn ringer off.
你为什么不把它打开呢？
Why don't you turn it back on?
我有过
I have
你妻子真的要生了吗，船长？
Is your wife actually in labor, Captain?
在悬崖边，先生。
On the precipice, sir.
水破了吗？
Water's broken?
迫在眉睫。
Impending.
有没有这样的，呃，
Having any of those, uh,
宫缩？
contractions?
好吧，既然你问了，
Well, since you asked,
现在就来,
right now,
相隔40米。
40 mics apart.
昨晚，她的叫声就像
Last night, she was tooting like
葛底斯堡重演的号手。
a bugler at a Gettysburg reenactment.
目前，她的宫颈是
Currently, her cervix is
两厘米扩张，开始打哈欠。
two centimeters dilated and starting to yawn.
好吧，这样的信息太多了。
All right, that is too much information.
是的，先生。
Yes, it is, sir.
飞行员们，看在上帝的份上，确保电话是开着的。
Airmen, for the love of God, make sure that phone's turned on.
谢谢。
Thank you.
接触。
Contact.
多辆车向内驶来。十一点。
Multiple vehicles inbound. Eleven o'clock.
哦，彼得罗夫开始行动了。
Oh, Petrov is on the move.
这些该死的家伙是谁？
Who the hell are these guys?
表明你们的身份！
Identify yourselves!
我也不知道。
Don't know.
当地民兵组织？
Local militia?
看起来有点像阿布沙耶夫。
Kinda looks like Abu Sayyaf.
毕晓普，你能确认一下吗？
Bishop, can you confirm?
是啊，我看不出来。
Yeah, I can't tell.
更多有枪的人。
More guys with guns.
当然，在他们离开之前，他妈的不会带走这个化合物。
Sure as shit ain't taking this compound 'til they leave.
看看从领头车左侧出来的那个家伙。
Check out the dude getting out the left side of the lead vehicle.
告诉我这不像赛义德·哈希米。
Tell me that doesn't look like Saeed Hashimi.
操。
Fuck.
那是谁？
Who's that?
阿布沙耶夫的头目。
Head of Abu Sayyaf.
他当然是来买枪的。
Sure he's here to buy guns.
睁大你的眼睛。
Keep your eyes open.
枪是为了安全起见。
Guns on safety.
JTAC，我们的空气状况如何？
JTAC, what's the status of our air?
收割机仍在坠落，大黄蜂待命。
Reaper still down, Hornet on standby.
你想让它升空吗？
You want it airborne?
否定。
Negative.
坐着别动。让我制定一个新的比赛计划。
Sit tight. Let me work on a new game plan.
哟，
Yo,
无人机修好了。
drone's fixed.
五分钟后交接。
Handover in five.
我准备好了。
I'm ready.
操。
Fuck.
《花花公子》
Playboy,
我是收割者1-0，回到空间站。办理入住手续。
this is Reaper 1-0, back on station. Checking in.
请求建立开销的许可
Requesting permission to establish overhead
收到。很高兴你回来了，死神。
Copy that. Good to have you back, Reaper.
网格如下所示，
Grid is as follows,
11月，维克多，1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5。完毕。
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8- 7-6-3-5. Over.
复制网格，花花公子。
Copy grid, Playboy.
我已经联系上了。
I have contact.
开放式圆形大院，一个大型混凝土结构，
Open circular compound, one large concrete structure,
以及一条向北穿过大坝的道路。
and a road heading north crossing a dam.
确认目标区域。
Confirm target area.
收到，你看到目标区域了。
Roger that, you have target area in sight.
我不知道哈希米和彼得罗夫在床上。
I didn't know Hashimi was in bed with Petrov.
哈希米是个恐怖分子。
Oh, Hashimi's a terrorist.
他一定是从什么地方买的枪
He's got to buy his guns from somewhere
来。
Come.
到这儿来。
Come here.
这位小姐看起来对此并不是很兴奋。
The miss doesn't look too thrilled about it.
是啊，这家伙绝对是个讨厌鬼。
Yeah, this guy's definitely a creeper.
她肯定有奇怪的危险感觉。
She's getting stranger danger vibes for sure.
哈希米和彼得罗夫坐在树上
Hashimi and Petrov sitting in a tree
我-S-S……
K-I-S-S...
操。
Fuck.
走开!
Go away!
跑!跑，跑，跑。
Run! Run, run, run.
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
把他带走！
Take him!
跑!
Run!
他妈的怎么回事，甜甜？我们这是在干嘛？
What the fuck, Sugar? What are we doing?
战鹰，我是阿尔法1号。
Warhawk, this is Alpha 1.
让敌人与平民交火。请求更新
Have hostiles engaging with civilians. Requesting updated
让他看清楚。
Make him see.
真主至大！
Allahu Akbar!
操我。
Fuck me.
哦他妈的..。
Oh fuck...
狗娘养的！
Motherfucker!
上帝啊！
Jesus Christ!
彼得罗夫
Petrov,
爸爸！
Papa!
去他妈的，甜心，我可不想看着这个混蛋从那孩子的头上掉下来。
Fuck this, Sugar, I ain't watching this asshole lob off the kid's head.
爸爸！
Papa!
肯尼，准备转移视线。
Kinney, stand by for potential diversion.
收割者，我们需要大院和帐篷之间的武器效果。完毕。
Reaper, we need weapons effects between the compound and the tent. Over.
收割者1-0。一架是地狱火导弹，收到。
Reaper 1-0. One by hellfire missile, copied.
爸爸！
Papa!
艾贝尔，毕晓普，你们有机会，你们去吧。金尼，放下那该死的炸弹。
Abell, Bishop, you got a shot, you take it. Kinney, drop that fucking bomb.
收割者，你是清白的！再说一遍，你是清热的！
Reaper, you are cleared hot! Say again, you are cleared hot!
收到。
Copied.
目标已锁定。
Target acquired.
武器被拿走了。撞击30秒。
Weapon's away. Impact 30 seconds.
不是的！爸爸！
No! Papa!
不要30岁。
Don't have thirty.
跑!
Run!
快跑，孩子。跑!
Run, kid. Run!
伙计们？
Guys?
这是个他妈的洞穴入口。
It's a fucking cave entrance.
肯尼，你正下方有敌人。别动。甚至不要呼吸。
Kinney, you've got hostiles directly below you. Do not move. Do not even breathe.
艾贝尔，毕晓普
Abell, Bishop,
我需要瞄准目标。
I need sights on targets.
艾贝尔，你当中锋。毕晓普，最左边。我站在极右翼。
Abell, you taking center. Bishop, extreme left. I'm on extreme right.
一对一。
On one...
就位了。
In position.
一对一。
On one.
三
Three
二,
two,
一,
one,
金尼！
Kinney!
操!
Fuck!
他妈的。艾贝尔，你的六个方向有五个敌人。五十米。
Shit. Abell, you've got five hostiles on your six. Fifty meters.
毕晓普，快走。我请客！
Bishop, move. On me!
好了，艾贝尔。
All right, Abell.
金尼我需要..。
Kinney, I need...
别动，混蛋。
Stay still, asshole.
帮帮忙，伙计们！
A little help here, fellas!
我在努力，伙计。
Trying, buddy.
金尼，我需要你为艾贝尔掩护一下。
Kinney, I need you to lay down some cover fire for Abell.
苏格。
Sug...
嗯。
Yeah.
我们出了点状况。
We got a situation.
不，他妈的。
No shit.
我们遇到了另一种情况。火箭弹十二点方向。来了！
We got another situation. RPG twelve o'clock. Incoming!
狗娘养的！
Motherfucker!
我抓到你了，伙计。我抓到你了。
I got you, man. I got you.
好吧。
Okay.
你很棒，伙计。
You're good, man.
不，你很棒，伙计。你做得很好。你做得很好。我抓到你了。
No, you're good, man. You're good. You're good. I got you.
医疗箱在哪里？
Where's the med kit?
我会把你治好的。
I'm gonna get you fixed up.
来吧伙计。医疗箱在哪里？
Come on, man. Where's the med kit?
金尼。
Kinney.
阿贝尔，阿贝尔。不，不，不。
Abell, Abell. No, no, no.
妈的，妈的。哦，他妈的！
Fuck, fuck. Oh, fuck!
阿贝尔倒下了。阿贝尔倒下了。
Abell is down. Abell is down.
你好?
Hello?
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
哦，操。阿尔法1号，这个花花公子。
Oh, fuck. Alpha 1, this Playboy.
金尼，
Kinney,
听我说。
listen to me.
我们正遭到两个双人火箭队的猛烈攻击。
We are taking heavy fire from two two-man RPG teams.
我需要一些炸弹到下面去！
I need some bombs down there now!
等等，那Abell呢？
Wait, wh-what about Abell?
艾贝尔死了。
Abell is dead.
他已经死了。我需要你集中精神，中士。振作起来。
He's dead. I need you to stay focused, Sergeant. Get yourself together.
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
收割者，我们正在东南面遭遇火箭榴弹火力
Reaper, we're taking RPG fire on the southeast side
在院子里。在我位置以南两百米处。
of the compound. Two hundred meters south of my position.
把你最大的东西给我。已清除热气。
Give me the biggest thing you got. Cleared hot.
收到，花花公子。我们看到目标了。
Copy that, Playboy. We have eyes on the target.
1由BLU 118提供。
1 by Blu 118.
放下武器。
Weapons away.
撞击20秒。
Impact 20 seconds.
炸弹在哪里，中士？
Where's that bomb, Sergeant?
二十秒！
Twenty seconds!
火箭筒来了！
RPG incoming!
操!加糖吗？
Fuck! Sugar?
加糖吗？毕晓普！
Sugar? Bishop!
哦，见鬼。
Oh, shit.
操!
Fuck!
你看到他了吗？
You got eyes on him?
他在烟雾中迷路了。
Lost him in the smoke.
操。
Fuck.
是他放的烟吗？
Did he pop the smoke?
我不知道。
I don't know.
花花公子，收到了吗？
Playboy, do you copy?
我看到他了。
I see him.
陪着他。
Stay with him.
死神？收割者，你在吗？
Reaper? Reaper, you there?
死神？
Reaper?
收割者，你在吗？
Reaper, you there?
我们到了，花花公子。
We're here, Playboy.
告诉我你们队的情况。
Give me the status of your team.
呃,
Uh,
起亚。
KIA.
好了，花花公子，让我们
Okay, Playboy, let's
按数字来做这件事。
do this by the numbers.
确认您当前的栅格位置。
Confirm your current grid location.
嗯。
Yeah.
呃,
Uh,
我在往东北方向走。11月，罗密欧，2-7-6-0-9-3-2-2。
I'm headed northeast. November, Romeo, 2-7-6- 0-niner-3-2-2.
我，呃--
I'm, uh--
我差不多是
I'm approx
离撤离点只有五步之遥。
five clicks from the evac point.
我需要你向前扫描500米，确保区域安全。
I need you to scan forward 500 meters and make sure the area is clear.
收到，花花公子。我们抓到你了。
Copy, Playboy. We got you.
向前扫描500米。待命。
Scanning forward 500 meters. Standby.
是的，这一区域安全了。
Yeah, area's clear.
这片区域看起来很安全。你可以动起来了。
Area looks clear. You're good to move.
花花公子，收到了吗？
Playboy, do you copy?
花花公子？
Playboy?
他在做什么？他在动吗？
What's he doing? Is he moving?
他吓坏了。
He's freaking out.
你得让他冷静下来。
You gotta calm him down.
嘿，花花公子。好消息。
Hey, Playboy. Good news.
直升机正在向撤离点进站。骑兵已经在路上了。
Helicopter is inbound to the evac point. The cavalry is on the way.
你得赶快行动起来，孩子。
You gotta get your ass on the move, son.
你得走了，伙计。我们走吧。
You got to move, man. Let's go.
来吧，士兵。
Come on, soldier.
站起来，走吧。
Get up and go.
我们开始吧。好的。
Here we go. All right.
你向前看。我抓到他了。
You scan forward. I've got him.
向前扫描。
Scanning forward.
告诉我你看到了什么。
Tell me what you see.
收割者，
Reaper,
我想我听到了卡车的声音。
I think I'm hearing a truck.
他是对的。
He's right.
我得到了来自西方的联系。
I have contact from the west.
卡车上路了，半个滴答声。
Truck on the road, half a click.
我从东边联系上了。
I have contact from the east.
看起来他们正在向《花花公子》的位置靠拢。
Looks like they're converging on Playboy's position.
花花公子，注意了。你的东西方目标都在汇聚。
Playboy, be aware. You have converging targets east and west.
你还剩多少条例？
How much ordinance do you have left?
一次是地狱之火。空中呼叫地面114。待命中。
One by hellfire. Air to ground 114. Standing by.
你想让那些大黄蜂升空吗？
You want those hornets airborne?
否定。
Negative.
好了，花花公子，Tally。盯着目标。你想做什么？
Okay, Playboy, tally. Eyes on target. What you want to do?
盯着它。
Keep eyes on it.
收到。待命中。
Roger that. Standing by.
收割者，你看到敌人了吗？
Reaper, do you have eyes on hostiles?
来自东部的确认敌方持有武器。
Confirmed hostiles from the east are armed.
他们是阿布沙耶夫人吗？
Are they Abu Sayyaf?
他们有武器。可以放心地假设。
They've got weapons. Safe to assume.
花花公子，收到了吗？
Playboy, you copy?
现在不方便说话。
Can't talk right now.
啊，他妈的。花花公子，花花公子。
Ah, for fuck's sake. Playboy, Playboy.
狗朝你走来了。
Canine coming your way.
你一定是在耍我。
You gotta be shitting me.
吉特。
Git.
操，花花公子。
Fuck, Playboy.
水牛比尔已经下马了。他正在接近你的位置。
Buffalo Bill has dismounted. He is approaching your position.
看起来他朝莱西走来了。
Looks like he's coming towards Lassie.
别动。
Do not move.
《花花公子》
Playboy,
水牛比尔在你的职位之上。别动。
Buffalo Bill is above your position. Do not move.
好了，花花公子。看起来莱西要回家了。
Okay, Playboy. Looks like Lassie's going home.
水牛比尔重新登上了宝座。
Buffalo Bill has remounted.
敌人正在离开派对。待命。
Hostiles are leaving the party. Stand by.
该死的。
Goddammit.
《花花公子》
Playboy,
水牛比尔和他的伙伴走了。卡车开走了。
Buffalo Bill and his buddy are gone. The truck is gone.
你可以清楚地看到你的北面500米处。
You are clear tracking 500 meters to your north.
在你1点钟方向的山脊上有一条小路。
There's a path up that ridge on your one o'clock.
嘿，花花公子，
Hey, Playboy,
你还好吗？
how you holding up?
我挺好的。
I'm all right.
你从哪里来的，伙计？
Where are you from, man?
俄亥俄州。
Ohio.
不，他妈的。
No shit.
我也是。
Me, too.
布鲁克公园。
Brook Park.
米德尔堡高地。
Middleburg Heights.
我们基本上是他妈的邻居。
We're basically fucking neighbors.
O-H
O-H.
I-O。
I-O.
七叶树同胞。
Fellow Buckeye.
经常回家吗？
Get home much?
嗯。
Yeah.
是啊，我就在那里。
Yeah, I was just there.
不得不埋葬我的父亲。
Had to bury my father.
哦，伙计。很遗憾听到这个消息。
Oh, man. Sorry to hear.
是啊，没关系。
Yeah, it's okay.
你们关系好吗？
Were you guys close?
嗯。
Yeah.
是啊，他是个好人。
Yeah, he was a good guy.
甜蜜十六日新闻，该死的七叶树
In Sweet Sixteen news, the fucking Buckeyes
把床上的东西都拉在VCU上。
just shit the bed against VCU.
第一轮。
First round.
想让我更压抑吗？
Trying to depress me more?
抱歉，伙计。
Sorry, man.
嘿，你在梅菲尔德岛上见过圣诞老人妈妈吗？
Hey, you ever got up to Mama Santas on Mayfield?
你在开我的玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
我高中的时候住在那个地方。
I lived at that place during high school.
太他妈好了。
Fucking great.
我知道，对吧？95年，我在那里遇到了我的第一任妻子。
I know, right? I met my first wife there in '95.
哦，是吗？
Oh, yeah?
嗯。我们是排队相遇的。
Yeah. We met in line.
我们都点了斯特龙博利。
We both ordered stromboli.
他妈的谁点了斯特伦博利？
Who the fuck orders stromboli?
我知道，对吧？
I know, right?
我以为这是命中注定的。
I thought it was meant to be.
而且确实是。
And it was.
直到它不再是这样，
Right up until it wasn't,
你知道?
you know?
我现在的妻子讨厌这些狗屎。
My current wife hates the shit.
她吃醋了吗？
She jealous?
不，伙计，更糟..。
Nah, man, worse...
她是素食主义者。
she's vegan.
啊，天哪。那更糟。
Ah, man. That is worse.
你怎么知道某人是不是素食主义者？
How do you know if someone's a vegan?
多么?
How?
他们会告诉你的。
They will tell you.
你现在离得很近了，伙计。跟上步伐就行了。干得好。
You're getting really close now, man. Just keep up the pace. Good work.
直升机上的预计到达时间？
ETA on the helo?
花花公子0-6，这里是黑鸟2-5，
Playboy 0-6, this is Blackbird 2-5,
从东面接近着陆点。
approaching LZ from east.
预计到达时间3英里，完毕。
ETA three mikes, over.
收到。
Copy.
收割者，我去着陆区的路怎么样了？
Reaper, how's my path to the LZ?
安全了。
Clear.
道路畅通。
Path is clear.
是时候离开地狱了，花花公子。
Time to get the hell out of dodge, Playboy.
谢谢你的眼睛，死神。
Thanks for the eyes, Reaper.
我很乐意这么做。
Happy to do it.
嘿，下次你来拉斯维加斯的时候给我写信。
Hey, drop me a line next time you're in Vegas.
我已经和冰上迪士尼有了很好的联系。
I have a solid hookup for Disney on Ice.
你把我搞糊涂了。
You lost me.
我可能会放弃这一点，
I might pass on that,
但我一直都在内利斯。
but I'm at Nellis all the time.
我在这呢，伙计。呼叫中央司令部。
I'm here, man. Call CENTCOM.
乌鸦中队。埃迪·格林。
Raven Squadron. Eddie Grim.
只要找收割者就行了。
Just ask for Reaper.
好的。
Will do.
黑鸟2-5，我看到了。LZ可用于提取。
Blackbird 2-5, I have a visual. LZ is clear for extract.
用I-R标记位置。
Marking position with I-R.
收到，花花公子。我已经标记了你的位置。
Roger that, Playboy. I have your position marked.
联系！我被击中了！我被击中了！
Contact! I'm hit! I'm hit!
花花公子，你受伤了吗？
Playboy, are you injured?
否定的！
Negative!
一定是撞到我的盘子了。
Must have hit my plate.
死神，敌机，东面100米。往南两百米。
Reaper, hostiles, 100 meters east. Two hundred meters south.
联系！黑鸟。我在着陆区周围有多个目标。
Contact! Blackbird. I have multiple targets around the LZ.
联系，黑鸟。西岭又多了三个敌人
Contact, Blackbird. Three more hostiles on the west ridge
小武器和火箭筒。
Small arms and an RPG.
你最好快点动起来。
Better move your ass.
RPG！
RPG!
他妈的!
Shit!
黑鸟，你能留在这里直到我们找到一个安全的着陆区吗？
Blackbird, can you stay in the area until we can find a secure LZ?
不，花花公子。LZ太热了。
Negative, Playboy. LZ is too hot.
以最快的速度回复你。
Back to you as fast as we can.
他妈的!
Shit!
收割者号，西岭。
Reaper, west ridge.
联系，花花公子。
Contact, Playboy.
又有三辆卡车直接通过了。
Three more trucks right through.
收割者，需要炸弹在西边300米处。
Reaper, need the bomb 300 meters to the west.
安全了！
Cleared hot!
收到，花花公子。
Roger that, Playboy.
托利。盯着目标。
Tally. Eyes on target.
呆在原地别动，混蛋。
Stay where you are, assholes.
放下武器。撞击20秒。
Weapon away. Impact 20 seconds.
目标被击落。现在他妈的给我滚出去。
Target is down. Now get the fuck out of there.
操!火力全开。
Fuck! Taking fire.
这还没做完呢。
This ain't done.
又有一辆卡车从西边驶来。
Got another truck coming in from the west.
天哪，我被压住了。
Jesus Christ, I'm pinned down.
他们是怎么看我的？
How are they seeing me?
这是他的闪光灯！
It's his strobe!
它们一定有夜视能力。他得关掉闪光灯。
They must have night vision. He's gotta turn his strobe off.
这是你的闪光灯，花花公子。关掉你的闪光灯。
It's your strobe, Playboy. Turn off your strobe.
从东面开火。放下你所有的一切。
Taking fire from the east. Drop everything you have.
花花公子，我是温彻斯特。我没有炸弹了。
Playboy, I am Winchester. I'm out of bombs.
黄蜂的预计到达时间是两个麦克风。
ETA on the hornets is two mikes.
花花公子..。这里是大黄蜂1号。
Playboy... this is Hornet 1.
输入PointOut Level。
Entering point out level.
我正朝东向西驶来。
I'm coming in on an east west heading.
收到，大黄蜂1号。
Roger that, Hornet 1.
我在目标网格以北200米处。
I'm 200 meters north of target grid.
所有火力保持在目标栅格以南。
Keep all fire south of target grid.
我再说一遍，所有人向南开火。
I say again, all fire south.
收到。请注意，这将是危险的近距离接触。
Copy that. Be advised this will be danger close.
是的，是的。已清除热气。
Yes, yes. Cleared hot.
收到。
Copy.
三，二，一！
Three, two, one!
他妈的!
Shit!
仍然受到来自西方的炮火！
Still taking fire from west!
收到，花花公子。准备再跑一次。
Copy, Playboy. Coming around for another run.
操!
Fuck!
去他妈的！
Fuck this!
你想要什么，飞行员？
What do you want, Airman?
-是的，我在经营星巴克。-动起来！
- Yeah, I'm doing a Starbucks run. - Moving!
帕克特上校正在崛起。
Colonel Packett is springing.
一件什么？
A what?
星巴克。
Starbucks.
你疯了吗？
Have you lost your mind?
飞行员，快走！
Airman, leave!
盯着那只大黄蜂。
Eyes on that hornet.
在西边的山脊上给我点火。
Give me some fire on the west ridge.
你已经完全脱身了。
You're cleared hot.
确认。西边还是东边？
Confirm. West or east?
西!西!
West! West!
收到。这一次将是危险的接近。
Copy that. This one is going to be danger close.
我们还是看不到你的踪影。
We still do not have visual on you.
没事的放下枪！你可以开火了！
It's fine. Just drop it! You're cleared hot!
请注意，这是危险接近。
Be advised, this is danger close.
高度。
Altitude.
拉起来
Pull up.
花花公子我是温彻斯特
Playboy, I am Winchester.
大黄蜂1号是RTB
Hornet 1 is RTB.
收到
Copy that.
好枪法
Good shooting.
情况如何，收割者
How's it looking, Reaper?
花花公子，从我们所看到的，它看起来很清楚。
Playboy, from what we can see, it looks clear.
这些混蛋知道我们在外面所以
These fuckers know we're out there now, so...
不要低估任何惊喜。
do not discount any surprises.
又有一个着陆点？
We got another LZ?
有一片空地
There's a clearing
在你东北方向两公里处
two clicks northeast of your position.
但你不会喜欢的。
You're not gonna like it though.
你说东北？
You say northeast?
A公司花花公子
A-firm, Playboy.
东北部是一座大山。
Northeast is up a big fucking hill.
我知道，伙计。我告诉过你，你不会喜欢的。
I know, man. I told you, you weren't gonna like it.
很抱歉，但这是我们最接近的着陆点了。
I'm sorry, but that is the closest LZ option we have.
花花公子直升机已经起飞了
Playboy, the helo is airborne.
预计到达备用着陆点的时间是90分钟
ETA to the alternate LZ is 90 mikes.
收到了吗
You copy?
我在听
Yeah, I'm here.
你好吗，伙计？
How you doing, man?
很毒。
Pretty gassed.
是的，毫无疑问。
Yeah, no doubt.
坚持住好吗
Hang in there, okay?
很抱歉撤离失败了，伙计。
Sorry about the failed evac, man.
现在你知道了
Now you know.
不要相信空军。传统上，我们都是狗屎。
Don't trust Air Force Captains. Traditionally, we are full of shit.
上尉？
Captain?
是啊
Yeah.
你说你在95年遇到你的第一任妻子。
You said you met your first wife in '95.
是啊，我老得跟屎一样。我现在应该是将军了
Yeah, I am old as shit. I should be a general by now.
我有三个前妻。我有八个孩子。我娶了个新老婆。我马上就要有新的孩子了。
I got three ex-wives. I got eight kids. I got a new wife. I got a new kid on the way.
我需要现役奖金。
I need the active duty bonuses.
如果我从上尉毕业，他们会让我当教官，所以去他妈的。
If I go out from Captain, they'll make me an instructor, so fuck that.
你在鸟前飞固定翼？
You fly fixed wings before the birds?
这是一个很长的故事，我的朋友。
That is a very long story, my friend.
但是，是的，最初，我确实报名成为一名飞行员。
But, yes, originally, I did sign up to be a pilot.
但显然空军认为
But apparently, the Air Force thought
我对权威的反应不正常。
my responses to authority were not normal.
所以那只山羊被干了。
So that goat got fucked.
真狡猾
Subtle.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
我把我的大嘴巴都说出来了，
Well, I shot my big mouth off,
我发现自己被重新分配到美国空军特种部队
and I found myself reassigned to USAF-SF
在一个鸟不拉屎的地方守了20年
guarding shit in the middle of nowhere for 20 years.
位于澳大利亚阿留申群岛松峡的埃雷克森基地。
Eareckson Base in the Aleutian, Pine Gap in Australia...
花花公子，收到了吗？
Playboy, do you copy?
是啊我在听
Yeah. Yeah, I'm here.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
从半山腰滑下来。
Slid halfway down a fucking mountain.
哦，妈的，伙计。你没事吧？
Oh, fuck, man. You okay?
你受伤了？
You hurt?
是啊只是我的骄傲。
Yeah. Just my pride.
收割机，我在花花公子前面有动静。
Uh, Reaper, I've got movement in front of Playboy.
西北方向100米处。
One hundred meters northwest.
放大。
Zoom in.
三名全副武装的敌人。
Three armed hostiles.
花花公子，有三个敌人朝你来了。
Playboy, you have three hostiles heading your way.
找掩护。
Find cover.
操。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Shit.
向前扫描。让我和他在一起。
Scan forward. Keep me with him.
收到。
Copy.
抓到他了吗？
Got him?
我在找。我在找。
I'm looking. I'm looking.
操。
Fuck.
我抓到他了
I got him
他往下游去了。
He's heading downstream.
他妈的该死的！
God fucking dammit!
帮我接上校。
Get me the colonel.
嗯。
Yeah.
继续找。
Keep looking.
我在树冠下跟丢了他。
I lost him under the canopy.
操。
Fuck.
收割者，什么是现场代表？
Reaper, what's the sitrep?
这项任务已经一团糟了，上校。
This mission has gone to shit, Colonel.
我有一项行动，他被带走了。
I got an op who's been taken.
我们已经开工12小时了。
We are 12 hours in.
我是温彻斯特，但我们不能离开目标区域，因为我们只有一只眼睛。
I'm Winchester, but we cannot leave the target area because we have the only eyes.
请求允许在我们把士兵带回家之前坐在轮椅上。
Requesting permission to stay in the chair until we get the soldier home.
你感觉怎么样？你感觉很刺激吗？
How you feeling? Are you feeling sharp?
哦，是的。
Oh yeah.
像大象的屁股一样锋利。
Sharp as an elephant's ass.
上士？
Staff Sergeant?
我很好，先生。
I'm good, sir.
好的，埃迪。坐在椅子上。
Okay, Eddie. Stay in the chair.
把它搞定，你们两个。
Get it done, you two.
你这混蛋。
Fuck you.
来吧，花花公子。
Come on, Playboy.
赶快。跟我说说。
Come on. Talk to me.
哦，见鬼。
Oh, shit.
抓到他了吗？
You got him?
所有这些都是关于JSOC资产的无线电闲聊。
It's all radio chatter about the JSOC asset.
谁?
Who?
那些家伙之所以出现在那里，
The reason those guys are there,
未确认，
not confirmed,
但一个是婆罗洲，另一个是也门。
but one says Borneo, the other Yemen.
也门？
Yemen?
那他妈的已经绕了半个地球了。你在耍我吗？
That's halfway around the fucking world. You shitting me?
这是谁说的？
Who's saying that?
从中情局或国土安全部的字里行间看出来。
Reading between the lines with CIA or DIA.
天哪。
Man.
字母汤狗娘养的！
Alphabet soup motherfuckers!
你不能相信他们说的任何一句话。
You can't trust a word they say.
举起手来！
Hands!
你受伤了吗？
Are you injured?
看我。
Look at me.
我以为你已经死了。
I thought you were dead.
这里。
Here.
把这个喝了。喝。喝。喝。
Drink this. Drink. Drink. Drink.
这里。把它穿上，好吗？
Here. Put that on, okay?
好吧?
Okay?
一枚火箭榴弹在你的位置爆炸。
An RPG exploded on your position.
就在附近，
Near,
不会的。
not on.
听。
Listen.
毕晓普被抓了。
Bishop got captured.
他伤得很重。
He's injured pretty bad.
我得走了。
I gotta go.
我们得回去接他。
We gotta go back and get him.
所以,
So,
拿上你能拿的东西，好吗？这里。
grab what you can, okay? Here.
拿着这个。这里。
Take this. Here.
把它们放在这里。把它们放在这里。
Put them in here. Put them in here.
给，拿着这个。
Here take this.
赶快。
Come on.
你在跟踪我吗，中士？
You following me, Sergeant?
嘿。看,
Hey. Look,
我懂了。
I get it.
这不是你想要的地方
This is not where you want to be,
但你得好好挖掘，好吗？
but you got to dig, okay?
它不在这里。它不在这里。它就在这里。
It's not here. It's not here. It's here.
毕晓普有麻烦了。
Bishop's in trouble.
我们得回去接他。
We gotta go back and get him.
好吧。
Okay.
你还能开枪，不是吗？
You can still shoot, can't you?
嗯。
Yeah.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
你的电池还在吗？
Still have your battery?
不，我是在秋天弄丢的。
No, I lost it in the fall.
让我看看你的刀。
Let me see your knife.
干什么用?For what？
What for?
我要给战鹰打电话。
I'm gonna call Warhawk.
带着水瓶？
With a water bottle?
来吧，你这狗屎。
Come on, you piece of shit.
收割者，这是花花公子
Reaper, this is Playboy
花花公子，你他妈的在哪里？
Playboy, where the fuck are you?
我是阿尔法一号的。
I'm with Alpha one.
我们要返回到最初的AO。
We're headed back to the initial AO.
不，不。否定。不，花花公子。
No, no, no, no. Negative. Negative, Playboy.
我们有情报资产已经找到了。
We have Intel the asset has been found.
我们不会去找资产的。
We're not going for the asset.
再说一遍？
Say again?
我们不会去找资产的。我们的一名队员被捕了。我们要进去抓他。
We're not going for the asset. One of our team members was captured. We're going in to get him.
花花公子，QRF正在组装中。待在原地等他们就位。
Playboy, a QRF is being assembled. Hold your position until they're deployed.
否定，死神。没时间了。
Negative, Reaper. There's no time.
与CJSOTF通话，让他们知道我们的情况。
Get on the horn with CJSOTF, and let them know our sitrep.
我们需要飞机待命。到达目标区域的到达时间是6-0英里。
We're gonna need planes on standby. ETA to target area is 6-0 mikes.
我们会确认网格的。完毕。
We'll confirm grid then. Over.
你往哪个方向走，花花公子？
What direction you heading, Playboy?
给我你的方位。
Give me your bearing.
花花公子？
Playboy?
通讯丢失。
Lost comms.
操!
Fuck!
帮我接通CJSOTF。
Connect me to CJSOTF.
我知道这很不寻常，艾琳。他妈的帮我接就行了，好吗？
Well, I know it's unusual, Eileen. Just fucking connect me, okay?
那他现在在哪？
So where is he?
不知道。
No idea.
有什么计划？
What's the plan?
投下一些炸弹，转移视线，
Drop some bombs, create a diversion,
进去把他找来。
go in and get him.
杀掉任何挡我们路的人。
Kill anyone that gets in our way.
你想把炸弹放在哪里？
Where do you want the bombs?
你是JTAC。你来告诉我。
You're the JTAC. You tell me.
也许最好的地方是沿着这条山脊线上的洞穴入口处。
Probably the best place would be along those cave entrances on this ridge line.
我们进去时，把他们隔开15分钟。
Space them out 15 minutes apart while we go in.
听起来不错吧？
Sound good?
听起来不错。
Sounds good.
找到毕晓普，在第一次袭击发生时采取行动。
Find Bishop, make our move when the first strike hits.
第二次打击应该引起他们的注意。
Second strike should hold their attention.
最后一个呢？
And the last one?
质量效应。
Mass effect.
让我们把那些洞穴翻个底朝天。
Let's turn those caves inside out.
他妈的A，孩子。
Fuckin' A, kid.
他妈的。
Fuckin' A.
是的，我在这里。你查到什么了？
Yeah, I'm here. What do you got?
B1满载？这将会完成这项工作。
B1 full payload? That will do the job.
我会确认的
I will confirm
收到时骨数为0-1的9行。
the 9 line with Bone 0-1 when received.
罗杰。
Roger.
B 1在空中，上校。
B1 in the air, Colonel.
收到。干得好。
Copy that. Nice work.
收割者，我是花花公子。
Reaper, this is Playboy.
收到，花花公子。我来了。
Copy, Playboy. I'm here.
好吧。游戏计划是使用CAS来打击一组洞穴结构
Okay. Game plan is to use CAS to strike a set of cave structures
在大院的北边，作为转移视线。
to the north of the compound as a diversion.
我需要三次攻击，间隔大约15英里，从1100开始。
I need three attacks spaced approx 15 mikes apart starting at 1100.
一千一百美元。记住这一点。
Eleven hundred. Mark that.
第一次打击，1100次。
First strike, 1100.
前两次袭击的目的是吸引他们的注意力。
Intent for first two attacks is to hold their attention.
最后的攻击应该有足够的弹药来瓦解洞穴中的所有敌人。
Final attack should have enough ordnance to neutralize all enemy in the caves.
三类中银。
Type three BOC.
11月，维克多，1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5。
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5.
再说一遍，花花公子。再说一遍。
Say again, Playboy. Say again.
11月，维克多，1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5。完毕。
November, Victor, 1-1-4-8-7-6-3-5. Over.
收到。
Copy.
眼睛盯着你。
Eyes on you.
三振出局。一千一百美元。转移视线。
Three strikes. Eleven hundred. Diversion.
11点15分，请转机。
Eleven fifteen, diversion.
十一点半，我们要把那狗屎点燃，然后把它炸飞去他妈的。
Eleven thirty, we're gonna light that shit up and blow it to fuck.
确认，花花公子。
Confirm, Playboy.
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
电池没电了。
Battery's dead.
我们还好吧？
We good?
希望如此。
Hope so.
花花公子，确认吗？
Playboy, confirm?
通讯丢失。
Lost comms.
操。
Fuck.
好了，我们都知道计划。
All right, we all know the plan.
你们今天在这里都做得很好。给我出去。
You both did some fine work here today. Get out of here.
不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
我们哪儿也不去。
We are not going anywhere.
我不是在问你。你完蛋了。
I wasn't asking. You're done.
你的八小时轮班时间已经超过十个小时了。
You're ten hours over your eight-hour shift.
好了，死神。从椅子上站起来。
Okay, Reaper. Out of the chair.
吃一袋鸡巴吧，霍金斯。
Eat a bag of dicks, Hawkins.
霍金斯？
Hawkins?
我是安德鲁斯。
It's Andrews.
赶快。让我扶你起来。
Come on. Let me get you up.
不是的。
No.
从椅子上下来，死神。
Exit the chair, Reaper.
我他妈的绝对不会退出这次行动。
There's no fucking way I'm off this op.
他妈的不可能。
No fucking way.
我有一辆起亚。
I got one KIA.
一次失踪。
One MIA.
我得到了两份他妈的疯狂的工作
And I got two fucking nut jobs
试图攻占整个阿布沙耶夫集中营。
trying to take on an entire Abu Sayyaf camp.
这就只剩下一个团队，也就是我们，
That leaves one team, i.e. us,
确保整件事不会在该死的篮子里下地狱。
to make sure this whole thing doesn't go to hell in a fucking handbasket.
你说完了吗？
You finished?
我还没说完呢。
I'm not finished.
我可以继续走下去。
I can keep going.
那么我建议你仔细考虑你嘴里说出的下一句话，船长。
Then I suggest you think very carefully about the next words that come out of your mouth, Captain.
哦，别这样，维吉尔。你要把军衔强加给我吗？
Oh, come on, Virgil. You're gonna pull rank on me?
你告诉过我这把椅子可以给我
You told me I could have this chair
直到行动结束。
until the op was done.
去看篮球比赛吧。
Go and watch the basketball.
先生，恕我直言，这是收割者的行动。我们应该被允许--
Sir, with all due respect, this is Reaper's op. We should be allowed to--
我不记得我问过你的意见，上士。
I don't recall asking your opinion, Staff Sergeant.
也许这就是你的问题，上校。
Well, maybe that's your problem, Colonel.
我强烈建议你不要走进同样的兔子洞
I would strongly advise you to not go down the same rabbit hole
作为你在这里的搭档。
as your partner here.
她一句话也没说，上校。
She did not say a word, Colonel.
一个字也没有。
Not a single word.
从椅子上下来。
Exit the chair.
离开房间，
Exit the room,
我会尽我最大的努力忘记这段对话。
and I will do my best to forget this conversation ever happened.
别他妈的搞砸了，朱尼尔。
Don't fuck it up, Junior.
没问题。
You got it.
第一次打击，1100次。这只是个消遣。
First strike 1100. It's just a diversion.
第二次打击11--
Second strike 11--
船长！
Captain!
我很好。我很好。
I'm good. I'm good.
你被解雇了。
You're dismissed.
我们到了。
Here we are.
眼睛。
Eyes.
一个人在帐篷里。
One guy in the tent.
阳台上有两个人。
Two guys on the balcony.
我们的时间是几点？
What's our time?
二十。
Twenty.
事情会变得很难看。
This is gonna get ugly.
我需要你集中精神。转着头走。
I need you focused. Head on a swivel.
如果你看到了我没有看到的东西，
If you see something I don't,
你说‘左接触，右接触。’
you say 'contact left, contact right.'
有人从我们后面走过来，
Somebody comes from behind us,
你可以说“六”。
you say 'six.'
剩下的我来处理。
I'll handle the rest.
只有在必要的时候才开枪。我们要尽可能长时间地保持沉默。
Only shoot if it's necessary. We got to keep this quiet for as long as we can.
不管它值多少钱，
For what it's worth,
你今天获得了第一名的地位。
you earned your tier one status today.
这是不是意味着我能拿到更多的薪水？
Does that mean I get paid more?
他妈的不是。只是听起来更酷而已。
Fuck no. It just sounds cooler.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
不是的。
Nope.
你?
You?
一直都是。
Always.
那，我们做吧。
Let's do it.
好吧。
Okay.
混蛋。
Fucker.
你还好吗？
You good?
嗯。
Yeah.
好的。
Alright.
他被卡住了。
He's jammed.
快，快！
Go, go, go, go!
赶快!
Come on!
枪是对的。正确的!
Gun right. Right!
移动!移动!
Move! Move!
我请客。
On me.
算在你头上。
On you.
左手边！
Contact left!
蹲下！
Drop down!
你还好吗？
You good?
操!
Fuck!
操。
Fuck.
哦，他妈的！
Oh, fuck!
手榴弹！
Grenade!
趴下!
Get down!
嘿，苏格。
Hey, Sug.
毕晓普。
Bishop.
这就是你的营救任务吗？
This your idea of a rescue mission?
我想我把它们放在我想要的地方了。
I think I got them right where I want 'em.
你看起来像个笨蛋。
You look like ass.
嘿,
Hey,
你好吗，毕晓普？
how you doing, Bishop?
跟我说说。
Talk to me.
啊.。
Ah...
空军，
Air Force,
我认为
I think
我们的处境很糟糕。
we're in a bad spot.
是啊，我们的处境很糟糕。
Yeah, we're in a bad spot.
嘿!
Hey!
嘿，哟！
Hey, yo!
嘿，听我说，伙计。
Hey, listen to me, man.
他们要向这些洞穴投掷炸弹。你懂的?
They're gonna drop bombs on these caves. You understand?
这些洞穴里有炸弹。
Bombs on these caves.
如果我们不离开这里，我们都会死。
If we don't get out of here, we're all gonna die.
你懂的?这些洞穴里有炸弹。
You understand? Bombs on these caves.
操!
Fuck!
愚蠢的混蛋！
Stupid fucks!
波音0-1，这里是阳光0-6。我们在追踪你的位置。
Boeing 0-1, this is Sunburn 0-6. We're tracking your position.
被建议埃塔首先进行无人机袭击，
Be advised ETA to first drone strike,
两个麦克风。
two mikes.
好了，让我们来他妈的摇滚吧。
All right, let's fucking rock and roll.
缩小400米。
Zoom out 400 meters.
我想他们知道
I think they know
我不会再坚持多久了。
I'm not gonna last much longer.
就--就--等一下，好吗？
Just-- just-- just hang on a second, all right, man?
我会想办法让我们离开这里的。
I'm gonna figure out how to get us out of here.
我已经出局了。
I'm already out.
快去找毕晓普，然后你们自己离开这里。
Just get Bishop and get yourselves out of here.
好吧?
Okay?
不，你很棒，伙计。你很棒，你很棒。
Nah, you're good, man. You're good, you're good.
不要.。
Don't...
他妈的摸他！
fucking touch him!
否则我他妈的就操你妈！
Or I'll fucking fucking fuck!
操!
Fuck!
他妈的狗屎！
Fucking pieces of shit!
赶快!
Come on!
把你他妈的手拿开！
Get your fucking hands off him!
他妈的胆小鬼。
Fucking coward.
加糖吗？
Sugar?
把你他妈的手拿开！
Get your fucking hands off him!
哈希米，
Hashimi,
你喜欢这样吗？
you like that?
加糖吗？
Sugar?
哦，操。
Oh, fuck.
加糖吗？
Sugar?
我很好。
I'm good.
操!
Fuck!
欢迎来到关塔那摩监狱。
Welcome to Guantanamo.
去。
Go.
你知道日本在1941年侵略了这些土地。
You know Japan invaded these lands in 1941.
嗯。建造这些洞穴的目的是为了留下来
Hm. Built these caves with the intent to stay
但我们的摩洛兄弟很快就打败了他们。嗯。
but our Moro brothers defeated them very quickly. Hm.
你知道他们建的这座大坝..。
You know this dam they built...
这是非常向前迈出的一步。
it was a very forward step.
是因为这血吗？
Was it this blood
从土地上被冲走
washed from the land
然后进入我们的嘴里？
and into our mouths?
但对我来说不是。
But not to me.
我们不对任何人负责，只对自己负责。
We answer to no one but ourselves.
我们度过了相当愉快的一天。
We were having a fairly pleasant day.
上帝保佑着...
Blessed by the...
那么，你怎么说呢？
Then, how you say?
有人给我们的游行泼冷水？
Someone rains on our parade?
除掉了一个帝国主义者。
Removed one imperialist...
只是为了再找一个。
just to find another.
这不是我们现在应该进行的对话。
This is not the conversation we should be having right now.
不是吗？
No?
我们该谈些什么呢？
What should we talk about?
我早告诉过你了。
I told you.
还有更多的炸弹在路上。
There's more bombs on the way.
阿,
Ah,
我对你的隐形炸弹不感兴趣。
I'm not interested in your faceless bombs.
你看，真正的结果
You see, real results
都是面对面创建的，
are created face-to-face,
相互作用，如
interactions like
你和我现在在这里做的事。
what you and I are doing right here.
说!
Speak!
其他突击队在哪里？
Where are the other commandos located?
没有更多了。只有我们！
There's no more. It's just us!
你们的喷气式飞机还在这片区域。
Your jets are still in the area.
一定有人在和他们交流。
Someone must be communicating with them.
我们在和他们交流。
We were communicating with them.
听,
Listen,
还有更多的罢工正在进行中。
there's more strikes on the way.
如果我们不离开这里，我们都是他妈的尘埃。
If we don't get out of here, we're all fucking dust.
不是的！你就是尘土！
No! You are dust!
该死的灰尘！
Fucking dust!
这是什么感觉？
How does this feel?
会这么害怕。
To be this scared.
太虚弱了，对自己的死亡无能为力。
Too weak to do anything about your own death.
你可能会认为我做这件事
You may think that I do this
没有任何感觉。
without feeling anything.
这是不对的。
That is wrong.
杀戮影响了我。
To kill affects me.
接受这件事的残酷性影响了我。
To embrace the brutality of this affects me.
这就是你和我之间的区别。
And that is the difference between you and I.
我看着一个人的眼睛，
I look a man in the eye,
我会让我的选择变得私密。
and I make my choice intimate.
炸弹！
The bomb!
对不起，你说什么？
Excuse me?
先生?
Sir?
我这里有一个我甚至不知道的东西--
I got this thing here I don't even know--
我都不知道这东西是否存在。
I don't even know if this is something that exists.
我妻子写下来了，所以她可能搞错了。
My wife's written it down, so she might have got it wrong.
听起来有点疯狂，
It sounds a little crazy,
但是
but, uh,
我得问问
I gotta ask, you know?
你是否有
Do you have
手工树坚果发酵植物基腰果
artisanal tree nut fermented plant-based cashew
还有塔希尼熏纯素新奶酪
and tahini smoked vegan new cheese.
有这回事吗
Is that a thing?
是啊，
Yeah,
就在这
right here.
很合我的心意。
Man after my own heart.
哈你我肯定会打赌的。非常感谢
Huh. I would have bet money against that. Thank you very much.
好吧，让我们他妈的摇滚。
All right, let's fucking rock and roll.
缩小400米。
Zoom out 400 meters.
他妈的表演时间到了。
It's fucking showtime.
准备开火。
Ready to fire.
投弹完毕
Bombs away.
六，五，四，三，
Six, five, four, three,
二一
two, one.
影响
Impact
我靠
Holy shit.
你是联合特种作战司令部吗
You JSOC?
你能走吗？
Can you walk?
你是谁？
Who are you?
喂！
Hey!
我操！
Fuck!
该死的肯尼
Fucking hell, Kinney.
你没事吧
You good?
是啊是啊
Yeah, yeah.
那家伙是谁
Who the fuck's that guy?
线人...
The asset...
我想.
I think.
快点。我们得走了。
Come on. We gotta move.
这么快？
So soon?
走吧
Let's go.
哪条路？
Which way?
我想是这边。我们继续走
I think it's this way. Let's keep moving.
妈的
Fuck.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
All right.
在这儿坐一会儿。我马上回来
Sit here for a second. I'll be right back.
波音0-1，这里是日炙0-6。你已接近目标。五分钟
Boeing 0-1, this is Sunburn 0-6. You are inbound to target. Five mikes.
收到我们很热。告诉我什么时候我能在7-9-8-4-0交叉伸展。
Copy incoming. We're hot. Let me know when I can cross extend at 7-9-8-4-0.
操
Fuck,
操操操
fuck, fuck, fuck.
来吧
Come on.
妈的
Fuck.
烤花生
Barbeque creepy peanuts.
耶!
Yeah!
来吧！
Come on!
纯素酸奶油。
Vegan sour cream.
来吧！耶!
Come on! Yeah!
植物基羊乳酪。
Plant based feta.
哦，你个混蛋！
Oh, you motherfucker!
妈的
Fuck.
拜托伙计
Come on, man.
快点。快接电话。
Come on. Pick up the fucking phone.
接电话中士
Get the phone, Sergeant.
中士！
Sergeant!
是的先生
Yes, sir.
死神我需要死神
Reaper. I need Reaper.
死神不见了
Reaper's gone.
打他手机
Try his cell--
等等等等等等
Wait, wait. Hold on.
702-166-42 00
702-166-42… 00.
耶!来吧！
Yeah! Come on!
等等，等等，等等！坚持住！
Wait, wait, wait! Hold on!
喂？
Hello?
我操！
Fuck!
6-42 00.
拜托伙计
Come on, man.
快接电话
Pick up the phone.
我在找我在看所有的架子。好吧
I'm looking. I'm looking at all of the shelves. All right.
嘿，
Hey,
等等
hold on.
不，我在看...
No, I'm looking at...
是个我不认识的号码。
It was a number I didn't know.
我在看所有的架子，
I'm looking at all the shelves,
但他们有真正的墨西哥菜
but they got real Mexican, you know?
但是里面有肉
Cou-- but with meat in it.
不，我不是...
No, I'm not...
宝贝，好了。
Baby, okay.
好了吗？里面有肉
All right? It's got meat in it.
抱歉，我不该用“真实”这个词。
Sorry I shouldn't have used the word real.
晒伤0-6，这是波音0-1。接近目标
Sunburn 0-6, this is Boeing 0-1. Approaching target.
快点。快走！走！
Come on. Move! Move!
好了吗？
Okay?
...因为
...tampon because
我想买一辆可降解的，
I wanted to buy a degradable,
没问题。你只管去吧。
No problem. Just go right ahead.
只是..。
Just...
你有什么问题吗？
what's your problem?
没什么。
Nothing.
好吧。
Okay.
人们是如此咄咄逼人。
People is so aggressive...
死神，我是花花公子。中止任务。我需要你中止行动。
Reaper, it's Playboy. Abort. I need you to abort.
取消最后一次罢工。我需要你中止最后一次--！
Abort the last strike. I need you to abort the last--!
操!
Fuck!
给情景喜剧打电话。
Call SitComm.
我不明白。
I don't understand.
去他妈的，给情景喜剧打电话吧。
Call SitComm, for fuck's sake.
呼叫情景喜剧。
Calling SitComm.
是!
Yes!
赶快!
Come on!
嗯!
Yeah!
来吧，王八蛋。接电话。
Come on, motherfuckers. Answer the phone.
排着队准备最后一轮比赛。
Lining up for the final run.
赶快。给情景喜剧打电话。
Come on. Call SitComm.
赶快!赶快!
Come on! Come on!
狗娘养的，
Motherfucker,
接那个该死的电话。
answer the fucking phone.
赶快!
Come on!
哦，他妈的。
Oh, fuck it.
操他妈的！
Fuck it!
在最终进场时加载0-1。
Load 0-1 on final approach.
赶快。
Come on.
移动!移动!
Move! Move!
就在那里。
Right there.
完成目标的时间
Time to target
30秒。
30 seconds.
伙计们！
Guys!
快点，快走！
Come on, move!
这是什么.。
What the...
撞击15秒。
Impact 15 seconds.
取消罢工！
Abort the strike!
我们有有效载荷。十秒钟。
We have payload. Ten seconds.
七...六...五...
Seven...six...five...
三二一..。
three, two, one...
波音0-1，中止！波音0-1，中止！
Boeing 0-1, abort! Boeing 0-1, abort!
你收到了吗？
Do you copy?
你干吗呢？
What are you doing?
他们收到了吗？
They copy?
嗯。
Yeah.
操作员
The operator
仍在目标区域。
is still in the target area.
犯傻呀。
Bullshit.
放大。
Zoom in.
放大
Zoom in
去洞穴
to the caves
罢工会发生在哪里？
where the strike was gonna be
他来了。就是他。那是《花花公子》。
There he is. That's him. That's Playboy.
抱歉，伙计。
Sorry, man.
该死的，死神。
Goddamn, Reaper.
谁..。
Who...
你在向我挥手吗？
are you waving at?
一个朋友。
A friend.
操!
Fuck!
谁赢了这场比赛？
Who won the game?
沃斯，宝贝。
Vols, baby.
八号精英。
Elite eight.
太棒了，上校，
That's wonderful, Colonel,
祝贺你。
congratulations.
这对你来说是一次极好的胜利
It's an excellent win for you
伟大的田纳西州。
and the great state of Tennessee.
没错。
That's right.
我刚打了那个电话
I just called that phone
他妈的五次。
five fucking times.
铃声又响了。
Ringer's off again.
现在不是我怀孕的妻子。
Now it wasn't my pregnant wife.
但对于现场的JTAC操作员来说，这是一个生死攸关的情况。
But it was a life-or-death situation for a JTAC operator in the field.
我们的工作是沟通！
Our job is communication!
我们的首要任务是保护男男女女
Our priority is protecting the men and women
为这个国家服务的人。
who serve this country.
所以如果你不介意的话，
So if you don't mind,
我们能继续他妈的工作了吗？
can we get back on with the fucking job?
见鬼，你以为你在做什么？
Hell you think you're doing?
上校，你可以把它从我的现役奖金中去掉。
You can take that out of my active-duty bonuses, Colonel.
嘿，睡一觉吧。
Hey, get some sleep.
明早见。
See you in the morning.
回头见。
See you then.
呃..。
Uh...
你没有燕尾服，是吗？
you don't own a tux, do you?
燕尾服？
A tux?
我没有燕尾服，没有。
I do not own a tux, no.
好吧。
Okay.
婚礼不是打黑领带的，对吧？
Wedding is not black tie, right?
不，不是黑领带。
No, not black tie.
婚礼就是这样。
The wedding party is.
你要请我当伴娘吗？
Are you gonna ask me to be a bridesmaid?
不，死神。
No, Reaper.
我想问你是否愿意陪我走过红毯。
I was gonna ask if you want to walk me down the aisle.
你是认真的吗？
You serious?
嗯。
Yeah.
哇。
Wow.
这将是我最大的特权之一
That would be one of the greatest privileges
我生命中的一部分。
of my life.
你知道一件事我知道..。
You know one thing I know...
百分之百肯定。
one hundred percent for sure.
你爸爸
Your dad
会为你感到骄傲的。
would be so proud of you.
谢谢。
Thank you.
那么，我们要跳什么舞呢？
So, what are we going to dance to?
跳舞?
Dance?
嗯。
Yeah.
哦，不，我还没想过这一点。
Oh, no, I have not thought about that yet.
好吧。好吧，你得选一首歌
Okay. Well, you got to pick a song
然后就听我的手说。
and then just listen to my hands.
我会听你的手吗？
I'm gonna listen to your hands?
哦，是啊。是的，你是。
Oh, yeah. Yes, you are.
哦，好吧。
Oh, okay.
哇，好吧。
Whoa, okay.
把这个绕到我的背上。
Run this round my back.
这?
This?
-那样的话，我知道它会从哪里来.-没错.这就对了。
- That way, I know where it's coming. - That's right. There you go.
好了，接下来是什么？
Okay, what's next?
进进出出。
Come back in and out.
出去。
Out.
然后回到我身上。
And back to me.
好吧。
Okay.
嗯。
Yeah.
然后出去。
And then out.
出去。
Out.
这一次。
This time around.
把另一只手给我。
Give me the other hand.
哦好吧。
Oh okay.
走过去。哦，在附近。
Walking over. Oh, around.
在我的背上。
Around my back.
漂亮的。
Beautiful.
你以前已经做过很多很多次了。
You have done this many, many times before.
我已经喝了几杯了。
I've had a few Dosey Does.
哦，你真的很棒。你真的很棒。
Oh, you're pretty good. You're pretty good.
任何其他的舞蹈。你知道怎么摇摇摆摆吗？
Any other dances. You know how to twerk?
给谁？对Terk？
To who? To twerk?
转到Terk。
To twerk.
-呃，不.我不知道怎么打瞌睡。-你最好开始练习.嗯。
- Uh, no. I don't know how to twerk. - You better get practicing. Yeah.